Here's today's news Scientists create chiral fermionic valve using quantum geometry principles.
Nokia pivots to AI, landing a $1 billion deal with Nvidia.
South Korea's Lee softens hardline stance toward Pyongyang.
Study links NSUN2 protein to cardiac hypertrophy and heart failure.
Marine ecologist Emma Johnston dies at 52, mourned broadly.
CBS New Year’s Eve Nashville special suffered a mid-show outage.
Brennan Johnson to meet Palace boss Glasner before transfer decision.
Review lists 2025 supply chain, AI, and cloud failures and one success.
Author Maggie O'Farrell reveals she wanted Paul Mescal to play Shakespeare.
EU's new green tariff on high-carbon imports officially takes effect.
Stay informed